<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>index on jemoka.com</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/tags/index/</link><description>Recent content in index on jemoka.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.jemoka.com/tags/index/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ADReSS Literature Survey Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhadress_literature_survey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhadress_literature_survey/</guid><description>The ADReSS Literature Survey is a literature survey for the results published during the ADReSS Challenge.
Antonsson 2021: disfluency + SVF features trained on SVM: lexical &amp;gt; narrative qual. Chlasta 2021: features extracted from VGGish on SVM; also trained new CNN from .wav. Sadeghian 2021: Used GA for feature sel., achieved 94% w/ MMSE alone; dev&amp;rsquo;d ASR tool. Martinc 2021: CBOW (text) + ADR (sound) late fusion&amp;rsquo;d to a BERT, ablated for features.</description></item><item><title>AP Phys C Mech Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhap_phys_c_mech_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhap_phys_c_mech_index/</guid><description>AP Phys C Mech is an examination held by the CollegeBoard in mechanics.
Things to Study Permittivity of free space Impulse Springs! In general. Perhaps review old notes. How to be faster? Kepler&amp;rsquo;s Laws of Planetary Motion</description></item><item><title>AP Statistics Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhapstats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhapstats/</guid><description>AP Statistics is an examination by the CollegeBoard.
See also crap to remember for AP Stats
Non-Focus Mistakes file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf Interpretation of regression outputs Backlog Chi-square file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf Notes confidence interval hypothesis testing t-statistics chi-square data inference binomial distribution</description></item><item><title>Differential Equations</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhdiffeq_intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhdiffeq_intro/</guid><description>Textbooks The textbook that we will be using is (Taylor 2011)
Assignments Challenge #1 The Unreasonable Effectiveness of Mathematics in the Natural Sciences</description></item><item><title>EB2022 Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbheb_emails/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbheb_emails/</guid><description>Presented Project80 Talks Person Society Keywords Email Chhavi Chauhuan, PhD, ELS ASIP AI Ethics, Pathology cchauhan@asip.org J. Elliott Robinson, PhD, MD ASBMB NF1, Dopamine, ADHD elliott.robinson@cchmc.org Jason Yi, PhD ASBMB UBE3A, Recklinghaus, Dup15q domain Erica Korb, PhD ASBMB Autism, Chromatin ekorb@pennmedicine.upenn.edu Catherine Wang AAA student approach to learning ??? Megan Fagalde, PhD Candidate AAA anatomy learning mfagalde@iu.edu Michelle A. Sveistrup AAA haptic abilities, HAT msveistr@uwo.ca AAA anatomy learning Alam Boyd AAA partner vs.</description></item><item><title>Financial Markets</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhfinancial_markets_intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhfinancial_markets_intro/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s not one market, there is a host of different markets. This field is filled with interesting markets which unique dynamics. The field can really be seen as an advanced statistics application, but its just happening to be modeling the case of financial dynamics.
Knowledge Random Walk Hypothesis</description></item><item><title>History Readings Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhhistory_readings_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhhistory_readings_index/</guid><description> Reading Date Notes New Deal Flip-book &amp;lt;2022-03-24 Thu&amp;gt; New Deal Historian Flipbook Legacy of McCarthyism &amp;lt;2022-04-25 Mon&amp;gt; Legacy of McCarthyism Soviet Perspective on the Cold War &amp;lt;2022-04-29 Fri&amp;gt; Soviet Perspective on Cold War MLK and Malcom X &amp;lt;2022-05-10 Tue&amp;gt; MLK and Malcom X Reading Origins of American Conservatism &amp;lt;2022-05-27 Fri&amp;gt; Origins of American Conservatism</description></item><item><title>Index Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhindex_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhindex_index/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of all indexes:
Projects Index Research Index Production Index About This should be reflected on a fancier way on my home page.</description></item><item><title>Linear Algebra Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhlinear_algebra_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhlinear_algebra_index/</guid><description>The bible stays the same: (Axler 1997)
We will be less exploratory, Axler will pretty much tell us. However, we should try to say stuff in the class every single class period.
There is a ban on numbers over 4 on this class.
Best Practices Ask questions Talk to each other Make mistakes From Riley: know the Proof Design Patterns Non-Axler but Important Things we explicitly are told to know, but is not immediately in Axler.</description></item><item><title>Nueva Courses Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhnueva_courses_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhnueva_courses_index/</guid><description>NUS Secondary School Other Duties AP Statistics Index AP Phys C Mech Index Tuning Forks bioinformatics NUS-MATH580 QIC Date Topic &amp;lt;2022-04-05 Tue&amp;gt; physical qubits, manipulating physical qubits &amp;lt;2022-04-08 Fri&amp;gt; making qubits interact &amp;lt;2022-05-10 Tue&amp;gt; Chiara Marletto &amp;lt;2022-05-24 Tue&amp;gt; Strong Free Will NUS-CS223 Algorithms Backlog: Finite State Machine
Date Topic &amp;lt;2022-04-07 Thu&amp;gt; stable matching problem, stable matching algorithm &amp;lt;2022-05-02 Mon&amp;gt; dynamic programming, relaxation &amp;lt;2022-05-23 Mon&amp;gt; distributed algorithum, randomized algorithum, complexity theory NUS-HIST301 American History Backlog: New Deal, Franklin D.</description></item><item><title>Production Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhproduction_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhproduction_index/</guid><description>This is a work-in-progress page listing all of my production projects.
Yappin: Podcast https://anchor.fm/yappin/
20MinuteRants: Blog https://20mr.substack.com/
Project80: Podcast See Project80.
Norman Stories: Fiction https://hidonipothan.substack.com/
(left) Director - Hillview Broadcasting: Production Studio https://hillview.tv/</description></item><item><title>Projects Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhprojects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhprojects/</guid><description>Projects Index is a index that contains a list of almost all projects for which I have ever worked on. Major categories are highlighted from chapter titles.
This index does not include my jobs; it is meant to be a list of endeavors for which I had key designing or founding impact&amp;mdash;not including many paid-jobs with an existing structure but including small one-off scripts and utilities.
Research Projects I have spent the last 6 years or so working as an actively-publishing data science researcher; my research interests are mainly in textual data mining, semantic analysis, L2 learning, and science education.</description></item><item><title>Research Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhresearch_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhresearch_index/</guid><description>I have done various published academic research projects in the fields of natural language processing and science education. Specifically, I have an interest in textual data mining, semantic analysis, L2 acquisition, and science education.
Computational Linguistics ConDef/Dictembed Wikipedia is a surprisingly good dictionary, and so we can mine it for building context-aware dictionary. Repository, Paper.
Title: ConDef: Automated Context-Aware Lexicography Using Large Online Encyclopedias
Collaborators: Zachary Sayyah - Nueva School</description></item></channel></rss>