<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>index on jemoka.com</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/tags/index/</link><description>Recent content in index on jemoka.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.jemoka.com/tags/index/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ADReSS Literature Survey Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhadress_literature_survey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhadress_literature_survey/</guid><description>The ADReSS Literature Survey is a literature survey for the results published during the ADReSS Challenge.
Antonsson 2021: disfluency + SVF features trained on SVM: lexical &amp;gt; narrative qual. Chlasta 2021: features extracted from VGGish on SVM; also trained new CNN from .wav. Sadeghian 2021: Used GA for feature sel., achieved 94% w/ MMSE alone; dev&amp;rsquo;d ASR tool. Martinc 2021: CBOW (text) + ADR (sound) late fusion&amp;rsquo;d to a BERT, ablated for features.</description></item><item><title>AP Phys C EM Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhap_phys_c_em_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhap_phys_c_em_index/</guid><description>Other Factoids charged flux Chapters coulomb&amp;rsquo;s law superposition electric field Gauss&amp;rsquo; Law electric potential current Ohm&amp;rsquo;s Law resistor kirchoff&amp;rsquo;s laws Capacitor Dynamic RC Circuits magnetism faraday&amp;rsquo;s law Things to do AP Phys C EM Things to Do</description></item><item><title>AP Phys C Mech Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhap_phys_c_mech_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhap_phys_c_mech_index/</guid><description>AP Phys C Mech is an examination held by the CollegeBoard in mechanics.
Things to Study Permittivity of free space Impulse Springs! In general. Perhaps review old notes. How to be faster? Kepler&amp;rsquo;s Laws of Planetary Motion</description></item><item><title>AP Statistics Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhapstats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhapstats/</guid><description>AP Statistics is an examination by the CollegeBoard.
See also crap to remember for AP Stats
Non-Focus Mistakes file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf Interpretation of regression outputs Backlog Chi-square file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf file:///Users/houliu/Documents/School Work/The Bible/APStats/APStats5Steps.pdf Notes confidence interval hypothesis testing t-statistics chi-square data inference binomial distribution</description></item><item><title>CLRS Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhclrs_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhclrs_index/</guid><description>Exploring CLRS.
2 insertion sort</description></item><item><title>Computer Systems Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhcomputer_systems_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhcomputer_systems_index/</guid><description>Notes on CS 107, C, MIPS, and computational systems.
Lectures SU-CS107 SEP272023 SU-CS107 SEP292023 SU-CS107 OCT022023 SU-CS107 OCT032023 SU-CS107 OCT042023 SU-CS107 OCT062023 SU-CS107 OCT092023 SU-CS107 OCT112023 SU-CS107 OCT132023 SU-CS107 OCT182023 SU-CS107 OCT202023</description></item><item><title>CS Probability Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhcs_probability_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhcs_probability_index/</guid><description>What random variable should I use? Unit 1 core probability, axiom of probability, counting, combination, permutation, DeMorgan&amp;rsquo;s Law.
SU-CS109 SEP272023 SU-CS109 SEP292023 SU-CS109 OCT022023 SU-CS109 OCT042023 SU-CS109 OCT062023 SU-CS109 OCT112023 Unit 2 SU-CS109 OCT092023 SU-CS109 OCT132023 SU-CS109 OCT162023 SU-CS109 OCT182023 SU-CS109 OCT202023 Result SU-CS109 Midterm</description></item><item><title>Decision Making Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhdecision_making_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhdecision_making_index/</guid><description>Lecture notes taking during CS238, decision making. Stanford Intelligence Systems Laboratory (SISL: planning and validation of intelligent systems).
Staff People&amp;rsquo;s office hours: https://aa228.stanford.edu/officehours/
Wednesdays, 5:30, Roble Field: ultimate Frisbee
Harrison Wed 1PM. AI Safety.
Arec Automotive driving, etc.
Elysia CS Coderm
Course Logistics &amp;ldquo;We will be working Taylor swift lyrics into every lecture&amp;rdquo;
Probability Will be reviewed in problem session on Wednesday.
High Level Programming You need to be able to code.</description></item><item><title>Differential Equations</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhdiffeq_intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhdiffeq_intro/</guid><description>Textbooks The textbook that we will be using is (Taylor 2011)
Content Simple Differential Equations solving differential equations Uniqueness and Existance eigenvalue applying eigenspace Second-Order Linear Differential Equation Non-Linear Systems SIR Model Assignments Challenge #1 The Unreasonable Effectiveness of Mathematics in the Natural Sciences</description></item><item><title>EB2022 Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbheb_emails/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbheb_emails/</guid><description>Presented Project80 Talks Person Society Keywords Email Chhavi Chauhuan, PhD, ELS ASIP AI Ethics, Pathology cchauhan@asip.org J. Elliott Robinson, PhD, MD ASBMB NF1, Dopamine, ADHD elliott.robinson@cchmc.org Jason Yi, PhD ASBMB UBE3A, Recklinghaus, Dup15q domain Erica Korb, PhD ASBMB Autism, Chromatin ekorb@pennmedicine.upenn.edu Catherine Wang AAA student approach to learning ??? Megan Fagalde, PhD Candidate AAA anatomy learning mfagalde@iu.edu Michelle A. Sveistrup AAA haptic abilities, HAT msveistr@uwo.ca AAA anatomy learning Alam Boyd AAA partner vs.</description></item><item><title>Financial Market</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhfinancial_markets_intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhfinancial_markets_intro/</guid><description>Why do we have a market? Basically: it allows society to make decisions about the value of things&amp;mdash;with the wisdom of the crowd. The stock market is how we (as people) decide what to make and how to make it.
Misc. Questions About the Market Misc. Financial Market Questions
Knowledge price Random Walk Hypothesis Brownian Motion Arbitrage Pricing Derivative Pricing options CAPM Stochastic Discount Factor GARCH ETF accounting price stock indicies VWAP short selling darkpool fundamental investing Second-Level Thinking stock market survey OTC markets NBBO LiquidNet</description></item><item><title>Fireside Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhfireside/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhfireside/</guid><description>Below you will find a list of the Fireside articles.
Article Date Welcome to the Fireside &amp;lt;2023-10-16 Mon&amp;gt; Make Models Go Brrr</description></item><item><title>Group Theory Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhgroup_theory_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhgroup_theory_index/</guid><description>Notes on MATH 109, group theory.
Lectures SU-MATH109 SEP272023 PSets These links are dead.
SU-MATH109 Problem Set 1 Course logistics midterm: November 1st, final: December 14th, 8:30-11:30 WIM assignment: December 8th, start of class (no late submissions) PSets: 8 in total, posted on Wednesdays at 8A, due following Tuesday at 8A</description></item><item><title>History Readings Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhhistory_readings_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhhistory_readings_index/</guid><description> Reading Date Notes New Deal Flip-book &amp;lt;2022-03-24 Thu&amp;gt; New Deal Historian Flipbook Legacy of McCarthyism &amp;lt;2022-04-25 Mon&amp;gt; Legacy of McCarthyism Soviet Perspective on the Cold War &amp;lt;2022-04-29 Fri&amp;gt; Soviet Perspective on Cold War MLK and Malcom X &amp;lt;2022-05-10 Tue&amp;gt; MLK and Malcom X Reading Origins of American Conservatism &amp;lt;2022-05-27 Fri&amp;gt; Origins of American Conservatism</description></item><item><title>Index Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhindex_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhindex_index/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of all indexes:
Projects Index Research Index Production Index About This should be reflected on a fancier way on my home page.</description></item><item><title>Linear Algebra Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhlinear_algebra_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhlinear_algebra_index/</guid><description>The bible stays the same: (Axler 1997)
We will be less exploratory, Axler will pretty much tell us. However, we should try to say stuff in the class every single class period.
There is a ban on numbers over 4 on this class.
Best Practices Ask questions Talk to each other Make mistakes From Riley: know the Proof Design Patterns Non-Axler but Important Things we explicitly are told to know, but is not immediately in Axler.</description></item><item><title>Nueva Courses Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhnueva_courses_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhnueva_courses_index/</guid><description>NUS Secondary School Other Duties AP Statistics Index AP Phys C Mech Index AP Phys C EM Index Tuning Forks bioinformatics PKM Intersession 2023 NUS-MATH580 QIC Date Topic &amp;lt;2022-04-05 Tue&amp;gt; physical qubits, manipulating physical qubits &amp;lt;2022-04-08 Fri&amp;gt; making qubits interact &amp;lt;2022-05-10 Tue&amp;gt; Chiara Marletto &amp;lt;2022-05-24 Tue&amp;gt; Strong Free Will NUS-CS223 Algorithms Backlog: Finite State Machine
Date Topic &amp;lt;2022-04-07 Thu&amp;gt; stable matching problem, stable matching algorithm &amp;lt;2022-05-02 Mon&amp;gt; dynamic programming, relaxation &amp;lt;2022-05-23 Mon&amp;gt; distributed algorithum, randomized algorithum, complexity theory NUS-HIST301 American History Backlog: New Deal, Franklin D.</description></item><item><title>Production Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhproduction_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhproduction_index/</guid><description>This is a work-in-progress page listing all of my production projects.
Yappin: Podcast https://anchor.fm/yappin/
20MinuteRants: Blog https://medium.com/20minuterants
Project80: Podcast See Project80.
Norman Stories: Fiction https://hidonipothan.substack.com/
(left) Director - Hillview Broadcasting: Production Studio https://hillview.tv/</description></item><item><title>Projects Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhprojects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhprojects/</guid><description>Projects Index is a index that contains a list of almost all projects for which I have ever worked on. Major categories are highlighted from chapter titles.
Research Projects I have spent the last 6 years or so working as an actively-publishing data science researcher; my research interests are mainly in textual data mining, semantic analysis, L2 learning, and science education.
For a list of my recent research, please head to the Research Index.</description></item><item><title>Research Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhresearch_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhresearch_index/</guid><description>I have done various published academic research projects in the fields of natural language processing and science education. Specifically, I have an interest in textual data mining, semantic analysis, L2 acquisition, and flipped/alternative learning.
Computational Linguistics ConDef/Dictembed Wikipedia is a surprisingly good dictionary, and so we can mine it for building context-aware dictionary. Repository, Paper.
Title: ConDef: Automated Context-Aware Lexicography Using Large Online Encyclopedias
Collaborators: Zachary Sayyah - Nueva School</description></item><item><title>Software Engineering Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhsoftware_engineering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhsoftware_engineering/</guid><description>process of Engineering: chronological order User Interviews + User Stories Requirements Analysis Documentation and Specification Build the damned thing Project Management and Development Methodology (SDLC) Task Estimation Software Design and Architecture Patterns Testing Build and Release engineering (TODO) Other topics Query optimization (TODO) Fucking acronyms to know AAA Method SOLID principles STAR method: state behaviorals in Situation, Task, Action, Results fundamental trade-off of Software Engineering The MIT vs. New Jersey problem: in Software Engineering, you can only choose one of FAST or ROBUST.</description></item><item><title>Stanford UG Courses Index</title><link>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhstanford_courses_index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jemoka.com/posts/kbhstanford_courses_index/</guid><description>Stanford UG Y1, Aut Decision Making Index Computer Systems Index CS Probability Index Speech Processing Index UG Other Duties Here are a list of random indicies which may end up being helpful!
CLRS Index AI Master Class Software Engineering Stanford UG Talks Date Topic Presenter Link &amp;lt;2023-09-20 Wed&amp;gt; UG Research Program Brian Thomas Stanford UG Research Program &amp;lt;2023-09-28 Thu&amp;gt; Bld an Ecosystem, Not Monolith Colin Raffel Build a System &amp;lt;2023-10-05 Thu&amp;gt; Training Helpful CHatbots Nazeen Rajani Training Helpful Chatbots Contacts Talk Contacts</description></item></channel></rss>